# Vanessa Schultz

7915 Delbonita Avenue | Las Vegas, Nevada 89147 | 702-332-8237 | schultzvanessa@hotmail.com

## **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

Marketing Professional with more than eight years of experience technical support, handling public relations, advertising, graphic design, and event coordination functions for several companies. Proven track record of exemplary performance, evidenced by having earned the Chairman's Award and Employee of the Month with most recent employer. Proficient with advertising through various social media platforms, including Facebook, Twitter, and Instagram.

For samples of Graphic Design, WordPress and Facebook samples please visit:

http://schultzvanessa.wix.com/vanessasportfolio#!project01/c1mgf

https://vanessavialpando369gmail.wordpress.com/

https://www.facebook.com/positivephysicalandspiritualwellbeing

Writing samples can be provided by request.

## **CORE COMPETENCIES**

Microsoft Office 2019 Suite	Quickbase and MRM	Content Management
Adobe Creative Cloud 2020	InDesign	Photoshop
Illustrator	Dreamweaver	After Effects
WordPress	Instagram	Twitter
		Facebook

## **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

Technical Support Representative, Telus International, Las Vegas, Nevada

2019 - 2020

- Tech-savvy with strong computer and software navigation skills.
- Personal experience troubleshooting personal electronic devices (e.g., personal computers, smartphones, tablets), online downloads, transactions, applications, software and hardware issues.
- Technical proficiency in web-based software and ability to quickly support platform and product functionality.
- Strong customer service orientation with an upbeat, people-minded personality and a willingness to go above and beyond for every customer.
- Ability to communicate technical issues in non-technical terms to customers.
- Ability to analyze problems/inquiries and research all possible solutions using all available tools
- Outstanding active listening and comprehension skills.

- Troubleshoot and resolve problems that an associate encounters with inventory.
- Use Problem Solve software to track customer issues and resolve them efficiently and accurately.
- Maintain over a 100% of all rate goal expectations.
- Full knowledge of all aspects of Amazon's production policies to train new employees.
- Adhere to all safety, quality, and production standards.
- Maintain over a 100% of all rate goal expectations.

Communications Specialist, Caesars Entertainment, Las Vegas, Nevada

2010 - 2017

- Wrote and proof read employee citywide communications for press releases, emails and printed advertisements for nine casinos which consisted of over 10,000 employees.
- Designed printed advertisements, maintained social media ad websites.
- Assisted the marketing departments with launching new guest programs and offers to employees with email blasts, printed advertisements, social media, texting programs and employee events.
- Volunteered and produced advertisements for community outreach programs, such as HERO and Code Green initiatives.
- Revamped back of house areas by having new branded wall wraps installed.
- Coordinated with Studio using or MRM submit design requests and receive printed advertisements.
- Sent all print requests to in-house print shops or outside print vendors.
- Implemented, advertised, coordinated and hosted employee events with the engagement teams.
- Ensured front of house and back of house employees viewed all current communications by posting them on informational bulletin boards, poster holders, table tents, banners and stand up signage.

Engagement Advisor, Caesars Entertainment, Las Vegas, Nevada

2009 - 2010

- Designed and copy wrote websites and print advertisements.
- Created, proof read and emailed out informational memos for employees and management.
- Maintained and edited video messaging.
- Launched and maintained social media and texting programs with Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest and Instagram and Hipcricket.
- Planned, coordinated and implemented employee events and programs. Created proposals and timelines for employee of the month programs, supervisor of the quarter, holiday parties, food drives, and other employee special events.

Assistant Communications Manager, MGM Mirage, Las Vegas, Nevada

2005 - 2008

 Managed and implemented employee events and communications. Organized event setups and hosted events.

- Designed, copy wrote and proof read printed and website graphic materials.
- Maintained and edited all video messaging. Oversaw and staff, schedules, outside vendor purchases and budgets.

Graphic Designer, The LINQ, Las Vegas, Nevada

2005 - 2005

- Designed and copy wrote brochures, invitations, magazine ads, posters, and other advertisements for casino special events.
- Managed the company's library of art and ensured quality printing.
- Maintained website and social media.

Graphic Designer, Review Journal Newspaper, Las Vegas, Nevada

- Designed and copy wrote advertisements for newspapers, inserts, and magazines.
- Collaborated with sales representatives and clients to meet their advertising goals.
- Maintained calendar, contact list of customer contacts and the dates they advertised.

## **EDUCATION**

*B.A., Communications*, UNLV, Las Vegas, Nevada GPA: 3.85 Emphasis in advertising, marketing, media and sales.

Associates Degree, Graphic Design, College of Southern Nevada, Las Vegas, Nevada

## **AWARDS**

Chairman's Award – Innovation Employee of the Month